This is a story about overcoming obstacles.
One day a farmer's donkey fell down into him.
well. The animal cried pitiously for hours.
as the farmer tried to figure out what to do.
Finally, he decided the animal was old.
and the whale needed to be covered up anyway. It just...
guess wasn't worth it to retrieve the donkey.
all of his neighbors to come over and help him.
all grab the shovel and began to shovel dirt.
into the well. At first, the donkey realises.
what was happening and cried horribly. Then...
to everyone's amazement he quieted down.
few shovel loads later, the farmer finally looked at the
down the well. He was astonished at what he saw with...
each shovel of dirt that hit his back, the donkey.
was doing something amazing. He would shake it off and take it.
a step up as the farmers neighbors continued to
shovel dirt on top of the enemy, he would shake it off.
and take a step up. Pretty soon everyone was in
as the doggy stepped up over the edge of the...
well and happily trotted off. Life is...
going to shovel dirt on you all kinds of dirt.
The trick to getting out of the well is to shake it.
off and take a step up each of our troubles.
is a stepping stone. We can get out of the deepest
just by not stopping never giving up.
Shake it off and take a step up.
you're not following the Biz Thoughts project, you're probably
never going to see us again but if you are can bring
threats. You're on a journey of continuous growth.